[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Worm casts (waste) is richer in nutrients and essential particles than the first 6 inches of topsoil.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these national costumes does not belong to a European nation?", "correct_answer": "Hanfu", "incorrect_answers": ["Tracht", "Kilt", "Kroje"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which two of these musicians were born in Lafayette, Indiana?", "correct_answer": "Axl Rose and Shannon Hoon", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael Stipe and Curt Cobain", "Kurt Cobain and Shannon Hoon", "Axl Rose and Michael Stipe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The names Robert, Robbie, Rob, Robin, Robyn, Roberto, Bert, refer to what?", "correct_answer": "Bright fame", "incorrect_answers": ["Long way", "Honorable master", "Mighty warrior"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this drama film, Penelope Cruz character, Mia, trains to be a nurse and is anxious to join the anti-fascist forces during the Spanish Civil War.", "correct_answer": "Head in the Clouds", "incorrect_answers": ["All About My Mother", "Vicky Cristina Barcelona", "Vanilla Sky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country borders both Slovenia and Slovakia?", "correct_answer": "Austria", "incorrect_answers": ["Serbia", "Poland", "Germany"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the two basic processes in calculus?", "correct_answer": "Integration and derivation", "incorrect_answers": ["Finding maxima and minima and solving second degree equations", "Composition and convolution", "Solving equations of sixth and seventh degrees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which characters drink tea together with the March Hare at the neverending tea party in Alices Adventures in Wonderland?", "correct_answer": "The Dormouse and the Mad Hatter", "incorrect_answers": ["The Duchess and the Mad Hatter", "Dinah and the Duchess", "The Gryphon and the Dormouse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Thallium?", "correct_answer": "Tl", "incorrect_answers": ["Ta", "Th", "T"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did Stanley Kubrick direct his Oscar-nominated film A Clockwork Orange?", "correct_answer": "1971", "incorrect_answers": ["1970", "1972", "1969"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What country was the largest producer of tomatoes in the world in 2008?", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["India", "United States", "Turkey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did Galileo Galilei invent the first telescope?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}]